Did you ever hear the words "Blue Sunshine"? Try to
remember...your life may depend on it.
Blue Sunshine is a science fiction, horror, mystery
film directed by Jeff Lieberman.
At a party, someone goes insane and murders three women.
Falsely accused of the brutal killings, Jerry is on the run.
More bizarre homicides continue with alarming frequency all over town.
Trying to clear his name, Jerry discovers the shocking truth...people are losing their hair and turning into
violent psychopaths and the connection may be some LSD all the murderers took a decade before.
Jerry Zipkin, played by Zalman King.
Alicia Sweeney, played by Deborah Winters.
Edward Flemming, played by Mark Goddard.
David Blume, played by Robert Walden.
Detective Clay, played by Charles Siebert.
Wendy Flemming, played by Ann Cooper.
Blue Sunshine is a 1977 American horror film written and directed by Jeff
Lieberman, and starring Zalman King, Deborah Winters, and Mark Goddard.
The plot focuses on a series of random murders in Los Angeles, in which the only common link between
the perpetrators is a mysterious batch of LSD that they had all taken years prior.
Over the years, the film attracted a cult following, and was released on
special edition DVD by Synapse Entertainment in 2003.
It has been shown at many film festivals since.
The film explores themes of lsd, drug use, epidemic, baldness.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and mind_bending.